const data = [
  {
    "category": "Music",
    "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94ff29",
    "correctAnswer": "Madonna",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Eric Clapton", "Nicki Minaj", "Alanis Morissette"],
    "question": "Which American singer released the album 'Confessions on a Dance Floor'?",
    "tags": ["music_albums"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "id": "62373f72f34f7d35cc389d6b",
    "correctAnswer": "Armenia",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Saint Kitts and Nevis", "Moldova", "Mongolia"],
    "question": "Yerevan is the capital city of which country?",
    "tags": [],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "624dba59de6018633d31f6c1",
    "correctAnswer": "Goldfinger",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Casino Royale", "Spectre", "Dr. No"],
    "question": "Which James Bond theme song was performed by Shirley Bassey?",
    "tags": ["james_bond", "film", "soundtracks"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "category": "Food & Drink",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f95029a",
    "correctAnswer": "Smoked Haddock",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Pickled Herring", "Spiced Basa", "Battered Cod"],
    "question": "What type of fish is in an omelette Arnold Bennett?",
    "tags": ["fish", "food"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "id": "624333bbcfaae40c129613fe",
    "correctAnswer": "A Drake",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["A Boar", "A Jack", "A Stallion"],
    "question": "What is a male duck known as?",
    "tags": ["words", "animals"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "id": "622a1c3a7cc59eab6f95107a",
    "correctAnswer": "Hydrocarbons",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Gases", "Petroleum Spirits", "Methylated Spirits"],
    "question": "What are Petrol, Naphta, Kerosine, Diesel and Oil?",
    "tags": [],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "category": "Arts & Literature",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f950177",
    "correctAnswer": "Macbeth",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Hamlet", "Othello", "Romeo & Juliette"],
    "question": "Which Shakespeare play opens with the 3 Witches?",
    "tags": [],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "category": "Film & TV",
    "id": "6257409d9da29df7b05f73eb",
    "correctAnswer": "Million Dollar Baby",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Lawrence of Arabia", "Vertigo", "Monsters, Inc."],
    "question": "Name the movie that matches the following plot summary: 'A woman works with a hardened boxing trainer to become a professional.'",
    "tags": ["film"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium"
  },
  {
    "category": "Science",
    "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f950588",
    "correctAnswer": "interactions between organisms and geomorphological processes",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "fossils of ancient life",
      "symptoms",
      "the effects of radiation upon living organisms"
    ],
    "question": "What is Biogeomorphology the study of?",
    "tags": [],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "hard"
  },
  {
    "category": "Society & Culture",
    "id": "6266e610ff2394bd44dee02e",
    "correctAnswer": "One",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Yellow", "Eight", "Ten"],
    "question": "In Spanish, what is the meaning of the word 'uno'?",
    "tags": ["language", "translations"],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "easy"
  }
]
export default data